Finding Aid for William Earl Porter papers, 1961-1972
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
William Earl Porter papers
1961-1972
Porter, William Earl.
8718 Aa 2
Professor of communication at the University of Michigan, chair of the executive board of the University's Center for Research on Conflict Resolution, and member of the editorial board of the Journal of Conflict Resolution. Correspondence, minutes, and reports relating to the administration of the Center and the Journal.
0.4 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of William E. Porter (donor no. 6058 ).
Periodic additions to the records are not expected.
The collection is open to research.
William E. Porter was professor of communication at the University of Michigan. He also chaired the executive board of the University's Center for Research on Conflict Resolution, and was a member of the editorial board of the Journal of Conflict Resolution.
The William E. Porter papers consist of correspondence, minutes, and reports relating to the administration of the Center for Research on Conflict Resolution and the Journal of Conflict Resolution. The collection is comprised of three series: Correspondence, Center for Research on Conflict Resolution; and Journal of Conflict Resolution Editorial Board.
Subjects:
Journal of conflict resolution.; University of Michigan--Faculty.Faculty.; University of Michigan. Center for Research on Conflict Resolution.
- Correspondence, 1963-1972
  - 1963-1965 (Box 1)
  - 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - 1968 (Box 1)
  - 1969 (Box 1)
  - 1971 (Box 1)
  - 1972
    - January-March 1972 (Box 1)
    - April-June 1972 (Box 1)
- Center for Research on Conflict Resolution, 1963-1972
  - Constitution and minutes (incomplete), 1963-1972 (Box 1)
  - Michigan Daily article, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Publications and staff lists, 1963-1965 (Box 1)
  - Research activities, 1963-1966 (Box 1)
  - Reviews of program, 1964-1967 (Box 1)
- Journal of Conflict Resolution Editorial Board, 1961-1972
  - Minutes
    - 1961-1963 (Box 1)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 1)
    - 1966-1969, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Miscellanea (Box 1)
  - Review, by Elizabeth Converse, circa 1969 (Box 1)